[
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word.Are they your friends? What do they __?",
    "Answer": "do"
  },
  {
    "Question": " Fill in the correct word. The news is __ the TV",
    "Answer": "on"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word. She was not well. So she ___ sing yesterday (അതിനാൽ അവൾക്ക് ഇന്നലെ പാടാൻ കഴിഞ്ഞില്ല)",
    "Answer": "couldn't"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word.Did she ____? (അവൾ പോയോ ?)",
    "Answer": "go"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word. This is ____ (ഇത് എന്റേതാണ്)",
    "Answer": "mine"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word. These are ____ books (our, ours)",
    "Answer": "our"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Write the complete sentence. How do you say this in English? --മഴയുള്ള ദിവസമാണ്",
    "Answers":["It's a rainy day", "It is a rainy day"]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct WORDS. It’s my book. Can you _______ ? (അതെനിക്കു തരുമോ)",
    "Answer":"give it to me?"},
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word. എനിക്ക് പട്ടികളെ ഇഷ്ടമാണ്. I like _____",
    "Answer":"dogs"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word. അവൻ വെള്ളിയാഴ്ച വീട്ടിൽ പോകാറുണ്ട്. He ___ home on Fridays",
    "Answer":"goes"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word(s). അവൾക്ക് മത്സ്യം ഇഷ്ടമല്ല. She _____ like fish",
    "Answers":["doesn't", "does not"]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word. I saw the video ___ YouTube",
    "Answer":"on"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word(s). നീ അവിടെ ആറു മണിക്ക് കാണുമൊ? Will you be there __ 6pm",
    "Answer":"at"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word. ഇന്നലെ അവൾ വൈകിപ്പോയി. She ____ late yesterday",
    "Answer":"was"
  }
]

